<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Published Works on Alex Curley</title>
    <link>https://www.alexcurley.com/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Published Works on Alex Curley</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 2024</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.alexcurley.com/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NPR’s 24 most anticipated video games of 2024 | NPR.org</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>I previewed five big upcoming games - Life by You, Homeworld 3, Manor Lords, Frostpunk 2, and Stormgate - in this annual round-up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best games of 2023, picked by the NPR staff | NPR.org</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>My thoughts on Age of Wonders 4, Terra Nil, Diablo 4, and Company of Heroes 3, made our round-up of the top video games of 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Total War: Pharaoh’ and ‘Star Trek: Infinite’: boldly going where we’ve been before | NPR.org</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>Two big strategy games debuted in the same week: Total War: Pharaoh, and Star Trek: Infinite. I took a deep dive into both in this standalone article.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detective Pikachu Returns, Assassin’s Creed Mirage and more Fall games reviewed | NPR.org</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>I reviewed Homeseek, the Frostpunk-esque city-builder, in NPR&amp;rsquo;s Fall 2023 round-up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Diablo IV&#39; Review: Activision Blizzard deals old-school devilish delights | NPR.org</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>Activision Blizzard&amp;rsquo;s blockbuster Diablo IV landed in May 2023 after much anticipation (and an impressive marketing blitz). I got to give the game a full treatment, including some custom gameplay GIFs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What doesn&#39;t kill you makes you a strong Black woman: Rico Nasty | Louder Than A Riot</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>I contributed some voice work for this episode on NPR&amp;rsquo;s (now former) hip-hop podcast Louder Than A Riot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Age of Wonders 4&#39; Review: This Magical Mystery Game is Hoping to Take You Away | NPR.org</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>Triumph&amp;rsquo;s Age of Wonders 4 topped my list of top strategy games in an otherwise disappointing year for the genre. I recounted my triumphs and tribulations in this full review on NPR.org.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NPR staff review the biggest games of March, and more | NPR.org</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>In March of 2023, I gave glowing reviews to Terra Nil, the post-apocalyptic city-builder, and the Diablo IV beta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyone Everywhere All At Once | Throughline</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>Ocassionally I will don an old-timey newscaster voice for Throughline, NPR&amp;rsquo;s excellent history podcast. I&amp;rsquo;ve made at least 8 appearances since the podcast began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NPR staff review the best new games and some you may have missed | NPR.org</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>Pharoah, the 1999 city-building classing, was resurrected in February of 2023. I wrote a short review for that Spring&amp;rsquo;s gaming round-up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Company of Heroes 3&#39; deserves a spot in any war game fan&#39;s library | NPR.org</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>I was complimentary of, but not blown away by, Company of Heroes 3 in my first standalone gaming review for NPR. Also my first official by-line on the website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The latest on the attacks in Ukraine | State of Ukraine</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>I produced and launched this news-responsive podcast, State of Ukraine, shortly after Russia began its invasion. This is the inaugural episode.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chugga Chugga CHEW CHEW! The Science of Misophonia | Wow in the World</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>I provided technical and production support for children&amp;rsquo;s podcast Wow in the World from their inception in 2017 until they left the NPR network in 2020. This is my last credited appearance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crickets And Cannibals: Unpacking The Complicated Emotion Of Disgust | Hidden Brain</title>
      <link></link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid></guid>
      <description>I tried baked cricket snacks in front of a microphone for Hidden Brain in 2018. They weren&amp;rsquo;t bad! I also provided the show with some voicework in 2019.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
